1.utilities.message_process中的convert_2_html soffice path是本机绝对路径，到时候记得改
2.file upload, there are two types of OpenAI API, Chat Completion and Assistants API(support file uplaod and add file in the context window)
But we are using Chat Compleltion API.
3.How does separate agents work, the agent call a tool node(hands off) that contains the command() object that jump to the destinated agent
4.数据生成直接html转excel
5. Our approach will use subgraphs instead of separate agents
6. use CoT in our prompt for LLM invocation

7. File paths to store: 

*上传了文件名
*具体内容存储地址
*